<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>things that happen to me</title>
    <description>hi i&#39;m josh let&#39;s be friends</description>
    <link>http://trommel.github.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://trommel.github.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 00:16:11 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 00:16:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>August 30, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Shoot, so I’ve been putting these posts off, again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, so this whole “write a blog post only every month” probably isn’t a great habit to be getting into, and, quite frankly, I don’t think that it’ll be too beneficial in the future, since the whole point of this is basically an “impossible to lose” journal that I can kind of share with whoever wants to read it. It was a cool idea when I started doing it, and looking back and reading those posts is actually really cool to do, even now, not even a year later. Thinking about reading those posts when I’m 30 or 50 or 90 or anything, really, makes me feel all nostalgic, already, even though I can’t really visualize it, yet. I guess that’s the whole point of these posts, though; nostalgia. That’s basically the entire point. History is cool because you can look back on cool stuff and think &lt;em&gt;“wow, that was really cool”&lt;/em&gt;. The future is cool, too, of course, but you can’t have good memories of the future, at least not yet (time travel or whatever might totally reinvent that, and that would also be pretty cool).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, I’m rambling. Sorry. Let me get to the point. If there even is one..?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, so, since I last wrote my last post, a couple of things have happened:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Our/My family went on vacation with my grandparents&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I got my first job (at McDonald’s (laugh all you want, everybody has to start somewhere))&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, that’s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vacation was pretty nice, and there was a pool and expensive drinks, so you know that it was definitely a cool place to be at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The job isn’t as relaxing (haha..?), but it’s, like I (kind of) said, a starting point, which is, obviously, important. It’s something I can stick on my résumé, which is always good. So far, I’ve had a couple of shifts, and as far as I’m aware, they’ve gone pretty well, so that’s cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and also, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/istx25&quot;&gt;Douglas&lt;/a&gt; got me a Canadian &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spotify.com&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; invite, since it’s in beta, for now, so I’ve been using it a ton. It’s a really cool service, and it has way more of a selection than things like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rdio.com/&quot;&gt;Rdio&lt;/a&gt;, however, Rdio has a nicer UI, in my opinion. One of the coolest things, to me, anyways, is that you can grab a Spotify URI, so you can just paste it in places as a typical URI using Spotify as the “protocol”, and the link will open up the song, album, artist, playlist, etc, right in the user’s Spotify app. This is probably not too awesome to people who might be used to this kind of thing, and I’ve used things like this before, but in a usage like this it’s really cool. For example, if you have the Spotify app downloaded right now, you can ~~&lt;a href=&quot;spotify://track:6tvt9vwh238mC2Sjl8c1WH&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;~~* copy and paste this&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;
spotify://track:6tvt9vwh238mC2Sjl8c1WH
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;into your browser to listen to what I’m listening to right now. Technology is so cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I guess I’ve kind of rambled my way through this blog post, so I should probably just close things up and try to be more “professional” in my next post, which I should be doing sooner, rather than later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, yeah, thanks for reading. That was cool of you to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Since Svbtle seems to block URIs that don’t either use HTTP or HTTPS protocols, &lt;code&gt;spotify://&lt;/code&gt; doesn’t seem to be working. &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/PGyEK6T.gif&quot; alt=&quot;David Tennant Sad in the Rain Gif&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 05:36:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/08/30/August-30,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/08/30/August-30,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>July 28, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Okay, so I haven’t written a blog post in over a month,
and that’s mostly because I really haven’t had much to talk about.
School consumes most of the interesting things that go on in my life, and,
whether I like that or not, it’s the truth.
&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.imjosh.me/june-4-2014&quot;&gt;My last post&lt;/a&gt; was on June 4, and I
wrote about CodeDay, which was extremely awesome, to say at the least.
I put that post off as well, because, if I recall correctly, I wrote it about
a week or two after CodeDay finished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put things off a lot. Even simple things.
Sometimes, I even put off things like watching movies,
and that’s the only reason I can give for still not having
watched any of the Batman movies (the new ones..?). I actually have a
list of around 50 movies that are regarded as some of the best movies ever
created, and I’ve put off watching them because I would rather fuck around on
my computer and do nautical nonsense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to change this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this blog isn’t going to be about that, because I don’t want it to.
I don’t typically come prepared for these things, mostly because I don’t
think or plan for when I’m going to write them. I kind of just look at the
calendar and think “oh, I need to make a blog post this month”, because I sort
of have a thing going where that seems necessary to me. I like documenting my
life to a certain extent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess I’ll just keep talking and see where it gets me.
Those aren’t wise words. Don’t quote them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, I’ve been working on a git project manager
called &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/trommel/oliver&quot;&gt;Oliver&lt;/a&gt; recently, and
I think it’s coming along nicely. I like the way it’s headed, and so
far it’s pretty sweet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also just came back from an “Advanced Programming with C# and C++ camp”
(we oddly didn’t even touch C++ whatsoever). It was pretty awesome, and I feel
like I learned a lot. The camp ran for a week, and I stayed overnight in a
building they had there (it was at
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.ca/maps/place/The+University+of+British+Columbia/@49.260605,-123.245994,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x548672cc2fd41e03:0xc79dd4e7732aa2f3&quot;&gt;UBC&lt;/a&gt;).
That probably sounds extremely vague, but I don’t remember anything else
about the location. This was my second year of this camp- last year I took
“Introduction to Java”. The camp was, like I said, pretty sweet. I had
an awesome time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had my birthday “party” yesterday, so a couple of friends and
I went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.ca/maps/place/Playland/@49.283883,-123.037117,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m6!1m3!3m2!1s0x548670de9cb3589b:0x2188f41801d8bea!2sPlayland!3m1!1s0x548670de9cb3589b:0x2188f41801d8bea&quot;&gt;Playland&lt;/a&gt;
(almost) all day, and we had a pretty sweet time. One of two of the friends
(one had to go home because he was busy the next day) “slept” over
(we ended up staying up until 6 in the morning, which was a terrible decision).
The friend that slept over left a couple of hours ago, and since then I’ve just
been watching College Humour videos in my pyjamas on my couch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Isn’t the Summer great?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 11:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/07/28/July-28,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/07/28/July-28,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>June 4, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today I’m going to write about CodeDay&lt;/strong&gt; on May 24th-25th. I’ve been putting off writing about it for a while because I’ve been busy, but I have a bit of extra time right now, so I thought “why not?”. I actually just happen to be wearing my CodeDay shirt today. Cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CodeDay started at noon&lt;/strong&gt; on May 24, which was a Saturday. My parents brought me down in our minivan, and we drove for 5 hours straight down to Seattle. CodeDay in Seattle was held at &lt;a href=&quot;http://porch.com/&quot;&gt;Porch&lt;/a&gt;, which is located &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/search/1551+Eastlake+Ave+E+Seattle%2C+WA+98103/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; if you’re interested. We got there a little early, so we went up to the room to see if anyone was there yet, and there was. We met Megh (I hope I’m spelling his name right, I apologize if I’m not), who works at Porch, who greeted us and let us look around inside. The inside of Porch is incredible. Just to give you a &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; brief overview of it, there are literally swings attached to the ceiling that are strong enough to support the weight of someone swinging on them. Just that alone should help you understand how cool it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By 11:45,&lt;/strong&gt; most of the other people had arrived. I didn’t know anyone, and, for whatever reason, I didn’t really strike up a conversation with anyone, probably due to the fact that 90% of the people I saw were at least 10 years older than me. I couldn’t find anyone my age, so I didn’t talk to anyone, which seems silly, and I guess it is. Or maybe it isn’t. I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When noon struck,&lt;/strong&gt; Megh let everyone inside and told us to go to the kitchen, which is where everyone swarmed to. We sat down at the picnic tables (yes, &lt;em&gt;picnic tables&lt;/em&gt;), and watched a film that one of the “CodeDay leaders” put on for us. The movie briefly explained how CodeDay works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After the movie was over,&lt;/strong&gt; anyone with ideas pitched them in front of everyone (about 125 people). We were then allowed to join groups with whoever we wanted. I chose to group with Prenay, the guy who pitched &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/trommel/studyline&quot;&gt;this idea&lt;/a&gt;. Then we got to coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About 20 minutes in,&lt;/strong&gt; Prenay realized he didn’t have the knowledge to code it, and most of the people who had joined the group by then were saying the same thing. About 8 people left the group, and I was left with two brothers, Jeremy and Dylan, who were completely new to programming. None of us had the knowledge to code it, so we decided to go to the workshops that a couple guys put on. There, they taught us the basics of Unity game development, as well as working with C#.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We went back to our table to work on a rolling ball game,&lt;/strong&gt; which is actually a lot more challenging than it sounds. We were essentially going to make a maze game where the player is a ball trying to get out of a labyrinth, but instead made an &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/trommel/spooky-sprinter&quot;&gt;almost horror game&lt;/a&gt;, in which the player has to get to the end of the level by dodging walls that will kill the ball. This has to be accomplished as quick as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This all took 24 hours.&lt;/strong&gt; During this time, I drank like 7 Dr. Peppers and had a lot of bags of chips. &lt;em&gt;I also ate a pack of M&amp;amp;M’s. Oh, how very wild.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At noon the on the 24th,&lt;/strong&gt; we presented our creations. Everyone had coded some awesome stuff. When we went up to present our game, the movement for the ball completely stopped working, so we sat down in shame, confused, since it had been working only 10 minutes before, and we hadn’t altered any code since then. But hey, next year, whatever we make, I’m sure it’ll work better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;10/10 awesome 24 hours of learning and coding. Would CodeDay again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 09:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/06/04/June-4,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/06/04/June-4,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May 26, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s been less than 2 weeks since I last wrote a blog post,&lt;/strong&gt; so I guess that’s good. I’m going to be writing about Friday (which was our school’s Swing Night (essentially a dance)) because &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Sophia_Anne99/status/470673956676988928&quot;&gt;Sophia wants me to&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll also be talking about &lt;a href=&quot;http://codeday.org/&quot;&gt;CodeDay&lt;/a&gt; in Seattle, which I had the privilege of going to over the weekend. Also, since I seem to mention the song I’m listening to in every blog post, I might as well do it with this one as well- I’m listening to “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WwOgXWOX-iE&quot;&gt;Leaves That Are Gone&lt;/a&gt;” by Simon and Garfunkel. It’s a good song.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday night was Swing Night.&lt;/strong&gt; Our school’s band puts on Swing Night once a year, every year, in May. It’s always exciting and fun to be a part of. Students in band class showed up at around 5 PM because Mr. Turi (our band teacher (which I think I mentioned in earlier blog posts)) bought &amp;amp; brought (I think Dominos) pizza for us. The pizza was pretty good. Then we helped set up for about half and hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People started showing up to Swing Night at around 5:30,&lt;/strong&gt; and doors opened at 6:00. I forget the order of what happened, so I’ll write the gist of it. Grade 8s started playing their music at 6:30. Our band class played at 7. A couple that Mr. Turi hired to teach swing dance showed up and taught everyone how to swing dance. I danced mostly with &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ashleyiscoo&quot;&gt;Ashley&lt;/a&gt;, but also with a couple other people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At some point during the night,&lt;/strong&gt; the junior and senior jazz bands went up to play. We (junior jazz) played 8 songs, which is relatively a lot. I played half and Maddie, the other bass player, played half. All I can remember from playing bass at Swing Night is that the amp was very loud and I made a couple mistakes and they were obvious and I was freaking out on stage because every time I made a mistake I freaked out and made another mistake and it was basically a cycle. I was kind of thankful when the songs ended and I got to sit down in a chair off stage and drink an Orange Crush that Adam had bought me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I danced with Ashley for a while longer,&lt;/strong&gt; and everyone kept making orgasmic and humping faces at me while I was doing so. Good times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swing Night ended at around 10:30,&lt;/strong&gt; but anyone involved had to help out help clean up, which we did until about 11. I went home and watched an episode of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2372162/&quot;&gt;Orange Is the New Black&lt;/a&gt; and then slept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Actually, I’m pretty tired now, so I’ll talk about CodeDay in the next blog post.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 12:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/05/26/May-26,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/05/26/May-26,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May 14, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hey.&lt;/strong&gt; The only reason I’m doing a blog post today is because &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Sophia_Anne99&quot;&gt;Sophia&lt;/a&gt; said she likes my blog posts. If it weren’t for her, I’d probably be sleeping (or probably on &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/&quot;&gt;Imgur&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alright&lt;/strong&gt;, so &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.imjosh.me/april-30-2014&quot;&gt;last blog post&lt;/a&gt; basically reviewed the holiday &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; back in March, so that’s pretty crazy. I’m getting caught up in the past, because, after all, the past is a cool place. Well, that’s depending how far you go back. Like, I wouldn’t want to be alive for the Black Plague or The Holocaust or anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I just realized&lt;/strong&gt; my blog is now going to be indexed by the word “holocaust”. &lt;em&gt;Fantastic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anyways,&lt;/strong&gt; I’m listening to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I_e49phsuRQ&quot;&gt;Further On Down the Road&lt;/a&gt; (the live version of the song is all I could find. Sorry), and coding a web crawler for &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LastHack/lasthack-crawler&quot;&gt;LastHack&lt;/a&gt;, a project I haven’t gone over in a blog post yet. I’m not sure if anyone who reads this post will find any interest in LastHack, so I’ll keep the description simple. &lt;em&gt;It’s a script that runs in the background, finding &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_source&quot;&gt;open-sourced&lt;/a&gt; projects, which you can use to improve your own code in various ways.&lt;/em&gt; If any of you have any use for that, go check it out. It’s a cool idea (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thetoxicarcade&quot;&gt;Cameron&lt;/a&gt; thought of it- I’m just helping him out).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today was a pretty good day.&lt;/strong&gt; I woke up and ate Nutella toast because that’s literally the best food in the world. I don’t care if it’s a “white girl stereotype”. Obviously white girls have a good taste in food. I went to school because that’s what kids do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My first class was Video Production&lt;/strong&gt; and it was fairly exciting. It could’ve been better, it could’ve been worse. We were assigned our last project of the year. It’s a pretty flexible project because we get to choose our own groups and the genre of the film, which is nice. I chose to work with Sami and Justin, and Alexis was put in our group because she didn’t end up choosing anyone. In the end, it’s a good group and I can work with them to make a (hopefully) good movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I had Band next,&lt;/strong&gt; which was also pretty fun. We played music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I had double block of English,&lt;/strong&gt; which is normally not a great thing, but in the end we had absolutely no work assigned. We watched an hour long movie about advertisement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At Lunch,&lt;/strong&gt; I went with Sami to the courtyard and showed him and his group of friends a comedy Sami and I had been part of / made for Video Production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the second block of English,&lt;/strong&gt; we discussed our thoughts and opinions on the advertisement movie for an hour. &lt;em&gt;Damn, son. Exciting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last block was Gym,&lt;/strong&gt; and we played Hockey. Half the class took everything too intensely and tried to injure everyone for the puck, and the other half took it as it is; Grade 9 gym class hockey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today was Tutorial Wednesday,&lt;/strong&gt; so school dismissal was an hour early. I showed some more people the video (the one I mentioned at Lunch) in the Video room. Then I walked with Sophia, Adam, Jamie and Ford to Camy’s, where Sophia met Parim, the awesome Pizza Guy. I said bye to Sophia and Ford, and sprinted up to where Adam and Jamie were headed; Ed’s Market. When I caught up to Jamie and Adam, Jamie told us some jokes regarding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TCvMB51i7JM&quot;&gt;Mr. Turi playing in his band&lt;/a&gt;. Adam bought me a Screamer (a slushee with soft serve ice cream- it’s absolutely delicious), and then we walked home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When I got home,&lt;/strong&gt; I spent about half an hour watching YouTube videos, and another hour learning Ruby on &lt;a href=&quot;http://teamtreehouse.com&quot;&gt;Treehouse&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m listening to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I_e49phsuRQ&quot;&gt;Further On Down the Road&lt;/a&gt; (the live version of the song is all I could find. Sorry), and coding a web crawler for &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LastHack/lasthack-crawler&quot;&gt;LastHack&lt;/a&gt;, a project I haven’t gone over in a blog post yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whoa that was cool&lt;br /&gt;
i looped the entire story&lt;br /&gt;
that’s crazy right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
aha ok cool&lt;br /&gt;
thanks for reading my blog post for today&lt;br /&gt;
bye guys&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 12:26:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/05/14/May-14,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/05/14/May-14,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>April 30, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Holy shit, it’s been over a month since I’ve last wrote in here.&lt;/strong&gt; Alright, let’s get to talking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alright, so since I last wrote, lots of things have happened.&lt;/strong&gt; I didn’t really go over what happened on vacation all the way back in March, so I’ll briefly go over that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Over Spring Break,&lt;/strong&gt; the family jumped in a car and hauled ass down in a minivan to Seattle. Vancouver to Seattle is a long drive. Four hours or something, I don’t remember. Then we hopped on a plane, which was actually pretty cool. We were with Virgin Airlines, and their style of “professionalism” differs quite a lot from generic airlines. It was a pretty good flight. I did stuff on my laptop- mostly making an app based on one of my friends, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Braeden_Mayer&quot;&gt;Braeden&lt;/a&gt;, called Braeviation (I forget how to spell it.) The app was influenced by planes because Braeden has a weird addiction to planes. I don’t know, ask him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When we got off the plane,&lt;/strong&gt; I saw a guy with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/wordpressdotcom&quot;&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt; shirt, so I mentioned it to my dad. He went and asked the guy if he worked at WordPress, to which the guy apparently replied with “yeah”. He then found us later before we got on our bus and gave me some free WordPress stickers, saying he “heard I was a WordPress fan”. Cool guy, and it was cool to meet a WordPress dev / employee. I think I shook his hand before we left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We arrived at our destination, which, by the way, is a cruise down to Mexico,&lt;/strong&gt; at about noon. But instead, we went and checked into a hotel, because the boarding for the cruise was the next day. While we were at the hotel, I accidentally uninstalled Ruby. I forgot to reinstall it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We boarded our cruise the next morning at some ridiculous time like 8 or something.&lt;/strong&gt; I was tired. I’m tired now. I’m almost always tired. &lt;em&gt;C’est la vie.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the ship we god our rooms and stuff.&lt;/strong&gt; We were assigned our own butler which was cool. His name was &lt;em&gt;Efrin&lt;/em&gt;, so naturally we started calling him &lt;em&gt;Zac Efrin&lt;/em&gt;. Good times. There was an ice cream machine on the cruise, and almost all food on deck is free, so I had a lot of ice cream. We were on the boat for one week and I must have had 47 ice creams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I played a lot of Guitar Hero in the arcade on the ship.&lt;/strong&gt; I think I spent at least $20 on that one machine. The cruise didn’t have internet (well it did, but it costed $100 for every 75 minutes on the internet, which is ridiculous), so we didn’t use it. I spent a lot of time programming random “projects”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We got off and explored Mexico on the third, fourth and fifth day.&lt;/strong&gt; Mexico is cool, but I prefer Canada. Not going to go into deep detail of Mexico because I don’t feel like it, but the food there was extravagant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the way home, we were told there was a surprise Disneyland visit booked,&lt;/strong&gt; so that was cool. I finally got internet at the hotel, so I pushed all my shitty code to GitHub. Disneyland was pretty awesome, and they had some new cool rides we went on, as well as the entire Cars town they had built. We stayed in Disneyland for 3 days before we got back on a plane and headed home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now we’re all caught up.&lt;/strong&gt; Cool. But now I don’t have time or enough energy to write anything about recently, so I’ll do that tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goodnight.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 16:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/04/30/April-30,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/04/30/April-30,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>March 28, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven’t written in a while, and, since I just came back from vacation, I thought  now would be a perfect time to start writing about everything that happened during the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I don’t want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 13:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/03/28/March-28,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/03/28/March-28,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>March 16, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I’m trying to think of how many things have happened since I last wrote a post.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lately I’ve been learning JavaScript, which is fun (and painful).&lt;/strong&gt; Using CoffeeScript has a pre-compiler makes it a lot easier though, as well as a lot more fun. I’m writing &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/trommel/pass.js&quot;&gt;pass.js&lt;/a&gt;, which is a password parser- which is essentially pointless, right now, anyways. With JavaScript / CoffeeScript, I’ve been coding a couple scripts based on things that are completely irrelevant to modern programming. They’re pointless, but they’re fun to make. I made a calculator based off my math teacher, Mr. Koo, appropriately titled “&lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/trommel/calkoolator&quot;&gt;Calkoolator&lt;/a&gt;”. I also made an even stupider script called &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/istx25/yogastar&quot;&gt;YogaStar&lt;/a&gt;, which “tracks how many girls with yoga pants you’ve seen today”. YogaStar might not still be on GitHub by the time you’re reading this because I gave the repo to my friend, Douglas, and he might have deleted the repo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s also Pi Day, so that’s cool.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;3.14159265359.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I can’t think of a lot to write about today, but I’m going on holidays tomorrow,&lt;/strong&gt;  which also means Spring Break, so I’m psyched. I’ll update more then.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 09:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/03/16/March-16,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/03/16/March-16,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>February 23, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today&lt;/strong&gt; I read &lt;a href=&quot;http://byjohnbrandon.com/why-blog&quot;&gt;an article I found interesting&lt;/a&gt;, written by &lt;a href=&quot;http://byjohnbrandon.com&quot;&gt;John Brandon&lt;/a&gt;. In the article, John talks about why he blogs, what it means to him, why he likes it, this, that and the other thing. He also says things that made me laugh at 12:27 AM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Blogs were invented in the mid 1800s by really bored Indonesian monks. This was before Blogger and Typepad, so they had to do all of the HTML coding by hand.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I don’t know why I chose today to blog.&lt;/strong&gt; I didn’t have anything prepared, but reading that article got me thinking about why &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; blog. Thinking over it, I believe it’s mostly because I want a permanent capsule of things I’ve thought about over the past however long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When I was six years old,&lt;/strong&gt; my grandpa bought me a &lt;em&gt;SpongeBob SquarePants&lt;/em&gt; journal, which I wrote in until it was filled from cover to cover. Doing so took me about three years. I wrote in it every time I had a thought in my head that I thought lasted longer than normal. If I had a thought that stuck to my brain and wouldn’t leave I wrote it down. I came to love the book because quite often I would write something down seriously and come back to read it years later, realizing how childish the topic was. I could laugh at myself, and it entertained me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A couple months after I had run out of space in my old journal&lt;/strong&gt; I received another one for my birthday (this time it was &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; themed), and continued writing down my thoughts in it. I’m currently reading them over, and millions of memories are flying back into my mind. These journals contained every thought that went through my head throughout elementary school. Even recently, before I turned all “eco-friendly” and started blogging, I’ve found some entries from grade eight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once I had filled out the &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; journal,&lt;/strong&gt; I went out and bought another one. I still haven’t filled up this one, and I probably never will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My point of this all is that blogging is incredible,&lt;/strong&gt; and that’s why I do it. It’s a way to vent to myself in the future by expressing what I think in the now. It’s a time machine back to the nostalgia I feel every day when I think about how fun it was being a child- not to say that I’m not still a child, although I have better memories from younger years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blogging is &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt; writing what’s &lt;em&gt;currently&lt;/em&gt; going on in my mind about the &lt;em&gt;past&lt;/em&gt; that I’ll read in the &lt;em&gt;future&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 16:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/02/22/February-23,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/02/22/February-23,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>February 16, 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hey guys, It’s been a while.&lt;/strong&gt; Like, almost a month. Um, I’ve been busy, so let me go over the things that’ve happened in the past month in code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;
relationship = [&quot;Josh&quot;, &quot;Mercedez&quot;]; break;
newProject = &quot;nuvel&quot;;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heh, code jokes.&lt;/strong&gt; Anyways, Mercedez and I broke up and I started working on a new project with Lakota, as well as &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/thetoxicarcade&quot;&gt;Cameron&lt;/a&gt;, a new friend. But really, almost nothing has happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I also started getting more into working,&lt;/strong&gt; which isn’t a correct English sentence. I’ve started caring more about grades because I don’t want to become a heroin addict and end up on the streets after getting C’s because that happens to a ton of people obviously. Even in the month that I’ve been gone I haven’t been involved with much that significantly interests me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I was invited to senior jazz band at school,&lt;/strong&gt; which is an honour. I accepted but, like I expected, I’m pretty far behind the level they’re at, so more practicing for me. I now have to wake up two times a week at 5:30 to get to jazz on time, but I’m not complaining because I’ll get extra credits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been playing a ton (fifty hours) of &lt;a href=&quot;http://steamcommunity.com/app/252490&quot;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt;, and that’s just over the past three weeks or so. No idea how I juggle jazz band, school / homework, projects with Lakota, and hours upon hours of Rust. Wait, that sounded egotistical. &lt;em&gt;I don’t juggle it, I do my best.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And sometimes I don’t have enough time to even do that.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;But that’s just an excuse for excellent work or whatever.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 12:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://trommel.github.com/2014/02/16/February-16,-2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://trommel.github.com/2014/02/16/February-16,-2014.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
